All right,Phoebe?
菲比
If I were omnipotent for a day, I would want world peace...
如果有一天我变得全能,我要世界和平
...no hunger,good things for the rain forest.
不再有饥饿,雨林不再遭受破坏
And bigger boobs.
还有更大的胸部
Well,see,you took mine.
你说了我的愿望
What about you?
钱德，你呢?
If I were omnipotent for a day, I'd make myself omnipotent forever.
如果有一天我变得全能 我要让自己变得永远全能
There's always one guy. "lf I had a wish,I'd wish for three more wishes. "
看吧，总有这样的人.  “给我一个愿望,我就要更多的愿望”
Hey,Joey.
乔依
What would you do if you were omnipotent?
如果你变得全能,你希望做什么
Probably kill myself.
大概是自杀吧
Excuse me?
什么?
If little Joey's dead, then I got no reason to live.
如果小乔依死了 我就没再活下去的理由
Joey,omnipotent.
乔伊，无所不能，不是无能
You are?
你是无能?
Ross,l' m sorry. I had no idea. I thought it was a theoretical question.
罗斯,对不起.我以为是一个理论问题
The One With the George Stephanopoulos
六人行 第1季 第04集 （克林顿亲信助手）乔治・史特喷那彼拉斯先生
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
How does she do that?
她是怎么办到的
I can't sleep in a public place.
我在公共场合根本睡不着
Libraries,airplanes, movie theaters....
图书馆，飞机上，电影院…
You slept at the Grand Canyon.
你居然在“大峡谷”睡着了
Hello,Mom and Dad never took us to the Grand Canyon.
父母从来没有带我去过大峡谷
Mom and Dad took us to the Grand Canyon?
难道父母带我去过大峡谷吗？
Would you look at her? She is so peaceful.
你看她， 睡得那么安祥
Yeah.
真的也
What? What? What?
什么事?什么事?什么事?
-Hi. -It's okay. You just nodded off again.
-没事 -你只是又打瞌睡了
What's going on?
你是怎么了?
I got no sleep last night. My grandmother has a new boyfriend...
我昨晚没睡好,我祖母有新男朋友了…
...and they' re both kind of insecure in bed,so And deaf.
他们俩在床上翻来覆去,还有耳聋…
They reassure each other that they' re having a good time.
於是两人不断确定,彼此是否尽兴
You have no idea how loud they are.
简直是吵死人了
-You can stay with Rachel and me. -Thanks.
-如果愿意你今晚可以和我及瑞秋睡  -谢谢
95,96,97. See,I told you.
95，96，97.我说得没错吧
Less than 1 00 steps from our place to here.
从我的住处到这儿不到一百步
You got way too much free time,man.
你浪费的时间太多了
There's the birthday boy.
他就是今天的寿星?
Hockey tickets. Rangers-Penguins tonight and we're taking you.
瞧,骑兵队与企鹅队今晚的曲棍球门票  我们要带你去看
-Happy birthday,pal! -We love you,man.
-生日快乐，老兄  -我们爱你
It's funny. My birthday was seven months ago.
你们真幽默,我的生日在七个月前
-So? -So you had an extra ticket...
- 所以呢?  - 一定是你们多了一张票
...and couldn't decide who got to bring a date?
找不到人一起去看
Well,aren't we Mr. The-Glass-ls-Half-Empty?
我们不是悲观之人
Oh,my God! Is today the 20th? October 20th?
天啊，今天是10月20号
-I hoped you wouldn't remember. -What's wrong with the 20th?
-我正希望你没记起来  -20号有什么不对劲吗?
Eleven days before Halloween. All the good costumes are gone?
万圣节的前十一天?  所有的好服装都被抢走?
T oday's the day Carol and I first...
今天是我和卡萝…
...consummated our...
…第一次进行…
... physical relationship.
…肉体接触…
Sex.
作爱
-You told your sister that? -Believe me,I told everyone.
-你告诉你妹妹了？  -相信我，我告诉了所有人
I better pass on the game.
我不去看球赛了
I'm just gonna go home and think about my ex-wife and her lesbian lover.
我还是回家,想着我的前妻和她的同性恋爱人吧
The hell with hockey! Let's all do that!
去他的曲棍球,我们回去一起想吧
Come on,Ross! You,me,Joey,ice! Guys' night out!
罗斯，别这样  你，我和乔伊，冰人夜游怎样
Come on,what do you say,big guy?
怎样，大个儿?
-What are you doing? -I have no idea.
-你打算干吗?  -我不知道
-Come on,Ross. -Maybe it will take my mind off it.
-拜托，罗斯  -好吧，或许能让我忘记伤痛
-Promise to buy me a big foam finger? -You got it.
- 但你要帮我买个大手指  - 一定
Look,look,look! My first paycheck!
大家看，我的第一份薪水
Look at the window! There's my name! Hi,me!
看看这框框，上面有我的名字 是我
I remember when I got my first paycheck.
我记起拿到第一份薪水的那一天
There was a cave-in in a mine, and eight people were killed.
矿场塌陷八人惨遭活埋
-You worked in a mine? -No,I worked at a Dairy Queen. Why?
-你在矿场工作?  -不，我在黛莉冰淇淋工作，干嘛问?
Isn't this exciting? I earned this. I wiped tables for it. I steamed milk.
真叫人兴奋，我赚来的 每天擦桌椅蒸牛奶
And it was totally...
这真是太…
... not worth it.
不值得了
What's FlCA? Why's he getting all my money?
谁是FICA? 为何他拿走我所有的钱?
I mean,what? Chandler,look at that.
我说，这是怎么回事 钱德，你看
This is not that bad.
没那么糟
You're fine,yeah,for a first job.
就第一份薪水而言,你已经算不错了
You can totally, totally live on this.
单靠它就够你过日子了
Oh,yeah. Yeah.
没错
-By the way,great service today. -Yeah.
-对了，优秀的服务员  -没错
-Hockey! -Hockey!
-曲棍球 -曲棍球
-Hockey! -Hockey.
Rachel?
瑞秋?
Oh,my God!
天呀
I swear I've seen birds do this on Wild Kingdom.
我发誓我在动物园也看过这种场面
What are you doing here?
什么风把你们吹来的?
We were in the city shopping,and your mom said you work here,and it's true!
我们到市区逛街,听你妈说你在这儿工作  结果是真的
Look at you in the apron. You look like you're in a play.
瞧你的围裙 好像在演戏一般
God,look at you! You're so big! I can't believe it!
-看看你，你的肚子好大，我简直不敢相信 -我知道
I know,I know! I'm a duplex.
我知道，我现在可是双人份的
IKiki,you look phenomenal. I mean, you've lost,like,a ton of weight.
你看起来不错. 你看来好像减了一吨重
And you should...
你真的是…
... really,really It's time to stop, you look perfect.
…真的是,是时候停下来了 你看起来很不错
What's going on?
发生什么事情拉？
Well,guess who my dad's making partner in his firm?
你猜我爸和谁合夥?
And while we're on the subject of news....
还有我们的话题
Look,look! I have elbows!
看，我有手腕
Passes it up to Leetch.
将球传给李奇
Leetch spots Messier. Here's the pass!
李奇看见纳斯有空档.一记妙传
We'll take a time-out while Messier looks at some women's shoes.
我们先暂停一下！ 让纳斯看看女鞋先…
Carol was wearing boots just like those the night that we first....
那一夜卡萝穿着那种靴子
You know? In fact,she....
你知道的?事实上，她…
She never took them off.
从没脱下来过
It's because we Sorry,sorry.
因为我们…对不起
I can't believe
我实在是无法相信
-What? -Peach pit.
-什么? -桃核
Yes,bunny?
怎么样?
Peach pit. That night,we had
那天晚上，我们吃了桃子
-Peaches? -Actually,nectarines but....
-桃子  -事实上，是油桃，但是…
Could've been a peach.
也可能是蜜桃
Then we Then we got dressed and I walked her to...
然後我们穿上衣服 然后我和她一起…
...the bus stop. I' m fine.
…走到公交车站.我没事
Hey,that woman's got an ass like Carol's.
那女人的臀部和卡萝的一样
What? I thought we were trying to find stuff.
什么?我以为我们在找东西
Come on,you guys. T ell me all the dirt.
好了，你们快点跟我讲八卦
Well,the biggest news is still you dumping Barry at the altar.
最大的八卦,还是你在圣坛前抛下巴瑞
-Let's talk reality for a second. -Okay.
-好了，我们来谈点正经的  -好吧
-When are you coming home? -What? Guys,l' m not.
-你打算何时回家?  -什么?我不回家
-Come on. This is us. -l' m not.
-拜托，我们是好姐妹 -我不回家
This is what l' m doing now. I've got this job.
这就是我现在做的,我得到了这份工作
I even do my own laundry.
我甚至自己洗衣服了
-This is what l' m doing now. -Waitressing?
-这就是我现在做的  -当女服务生
I' m not just waitressing. I mean,l' m....
我不只是当女服务生 我是说…
I write the specials on the specials board.
我写下每日特餐
And I take the dead flowers out of the vase.
摘下瓶中枯死的花朵
Sometimes Arturo lets me put the chocolate blobbies on the cookies.
有时老板还会让我在饼乾上涂上巧克力酱
Well,your mom didn't tell us about the blobbies.
你妈没有提起巧克力酱
Hey,Rach. How was it with your friends?
瑞秋，和朋友聊得如何?
Okay,how would you like some Tiki Death punch?
想喝杯鸡尾酒吗?
-What's that? -Well,it's rum and
-那是什么? -是郎姆酒,还有
Okay.
知道了
Since Phoebe's staying, we'll have a slumber party.
既然菲此要来过夜谈通宵
We got trashy magazines. We got cookie dough. We got Twister.
我们就买了一些八卦杂志 饼乾面团和扭体游戏
And I brought Operation. But I lost the tweezers so we can't operate.
我带了“手术”游戏来 不过我把镊子弄丢了,所以
But we can prep the guy.
不过我们可以演练下
-Rach,it's the Visa card people. -Oh,God. Ask them what they want.
-瑞秋，是信用卡的人打来的 -问他们想干什么
Could you please tell me what this is in reference to?
请问有什么事吗?
There's been unusual activity on your account.
他们说你的帐户有问题
I haven't used my card in weeks.
可是我已好几个星期没刷卡了
That is the unusual activity.
问题就出在这儿
They wanna see if you're okay.
他们想知道你是否没事
They wanna know if I'm okay? Okay,let's see.
他们想知道我是否没事? 我想看看
Well,let's see. The FlCA guys took all my money.
好吧，让我看看. FICA把我的钱全拿走了
Everyone is getting married or pregnant or promoted.
我认识的朋友不是怀孕就是升职
And I'm getting coffee. And it's not even for me!
而我只是端咖啡 而且还不是端给自己喝
If that sounds like I'm okay, then tell them I'm okay. Okay?
如果这样叫没事的话 就告诉他们我没事，好吗?
Rachel has left the building. Can you call back?
瑞秋刚出去，你能再打来吗?
All right! Come on!
好吧
Let's play Twister!
我们来玩扭体游戏吧
-Sorry. -Sorry. Sorry,sorry.
-对不起 -对不起,对不起,对不起
There was ice that night with Carol? Plastic seats?
你和卡萝来的那一夜有冰? 塑胶座位?
Four thousand angry Pittsburgh fans?
四千名愤怒的匹兹堡球迷?
No,I was just saying we're not sitting together.
不，我是说 我们可能不会坐在一起
But now that you mention it, there was ice that night.
既然你已提起,没错,那一夜有结冰
It was the first frost.
第一次结霜
Sit. Just sit down. Sit.
坐下吧
You're doing this amazing independent thing.
你应该感到自豪 你正在学习了不起的独立
Monica,what is so amazing?
摩妮卡，有什么了不起可言?
I gave up,like,everything. And for what?
我放弃一切 到底是为了什么?
-You are just like Jack. -Jack from downstairs?
-你和杰克没两样 -楼下的杰克?
No,Jack and the Beanstalk.
不，是杰克与魔豆
Ah,the other Jack.
另一个杰克
Right. He gave up something but then he got those magic beans.
对，他放弃某些东西 但是得到了魔豆
And then he woke up and there was this big plant...
他起床后 发现有棵大树…
...outside of his window, full of possibilities.
…在他的窗户外面 充满一切可能
He lived in a village, and you live in the Village.
他住在一个村庄 你住在一个村庄…
Okay. But,Pheebs,Jack gave up a cow. I gave up an orthodontist.
菲此，杰克放弃了牛 我放弃了一个整牙医生
-Okay,I know I didn't love him.... -Oh,see,Jack did love the cow.
-我知道我并不喜欢他 -杰克深爱着那头牛
But,see,it was a plan. It was clear.
那是有预谋的,一切都很清楚
Everything was figured out. Now it's like....
一切都会发生,就好像…
-Floopy? -Yeah.
-很简单的情况? -对
We don't know where we' re going.
我们也常不知自己何去何从
It's all gonna come together and it's just gonna be un-floopy.
你得仔细想清楚 自然就能步上轨道
Yeah,like that's a word.
对，真能拼
Okay. But Monica,what if it doesn't come together?
好吧，摩尼卡，但如果无法步上轨道呢?
Pheebs?
菲比?
Well,because you just I don't like this question.
因为你… 我不喜欢这个问题
See,you guys? What if we don't get magic beans?
瞧，如果我们没拿到魔豆呢?
I mean,what if all we've got are beans?
如果只拿到一般的豆子呢?
Get him! Get him! Get him!
宰掉他…宰掉他…
Yes! You're not laughing now, are you,pal?
笑不出来了吧，老兄
All you needed were guys hitting each other with sticks.
那正是你需要的 群以棍子互打的无齿之徒
Pass it! Pass it!
快传，快传
-He's open! He's open! -Shoot it! Shoot it!
-他有空档 -射门,射门
Hey,look,we're on that TV thing.
瞧，我们上电视了
Excuse me?
对不起？
It says to call if you're not satisfied with this candy bar.
上面说不满意这条巧克力糖 可以拨这个号码
Well,I'm not completely satisfied.
我并不满意
Well,the label promises nutty goodness.
好吧，标签上承诺的是坚果的品质
It's an emergency. But you know that, or we'd be in the predicament room.
这是紧急事件,我想你很清楚 否则我们就不会在这儿了
Hold on. Fill these out. Sit over there!
等等，拿去填资料 坐在那儿填
I don't want to make any trouble but I'm in a lot of pain.
我不想惹麻烦,好吗? 我现在很疼
-My face is dented. -Well,you'll have to wait your turn.
-我的脸凹下去了 -你得照顺序来
-How long do you think it will be? -Any minute now.
-大概要等多久? -快了
Hey,this
嘿,这是…
I' m so sorry,you guys. I didn't mean to bring you down.
真是对不起,我不是存心让你们不开心的
No,you were right. I don't have a plan.
不，你说得对 我的人生毫无计划
-Pizza guy. -Food!
-送披萨的  -食物终于来了
-Phoebe? -What?
-菲比 -干吗?
-Do you have a plan? -I don't even have a " pla. "
-你有计划吗? -我根本毫无计划
One mushroom,green pepper and onion?
磨菇，青椒和洋葱
No,no,no. That's not what we ordered!
-不 -不，这不是我们点的
We ordered a fat-free crust with extra cheese!
我们点的是奶酪脆皮口味
Wait. You' re not G. Stephanopoulos? Man,my dad's gonna kill me!
史先生不住这儿?没这个人 惨了，我爸一定会宰掉我的
Wait! Did you say G. Stephanopoulos?
等等，你是说史先生?
Yeah,this one goes across the street. I gave him yours. Bonehead! Bonehead!
对，他住对街 我一定是送错了，笨
When you do that, you're only hitting yourself.
当你这么做的时候 你不过是在打击你自己
Was this a small Mediterranean guy with curiously intelligent good looks?
是不是那个矮小的地中海人 一幅聪明样的帅哥?
-That sounds right. -Was he wearing a stunning blue suit?
-对，应该就是他 -他穿着迷人的蓝色西装?
-And a power tie? -No,pretty much just a towel.
-打着领带? -不，他只围一条浴巾
-Oh,God! -You guys want me to take this back?
-上帝呀 -你们忍心让我把它带回去?
What,are you nuts? We've got George Stephanopoulos' pizza!
什么?开什么玩笑  我们要吃史先生的披萨
Pheebs,who's George Snuffleupagus?
菲此，史先生是谁?
That's Big Bird's friend.
大鸟的朋友
-I see pizza! -I want to see. Let me see.
-我看见披萨  -让我看
Hello! Who are we spying on?
我们在偷瞄谁?
White House adviser, Clinton's campaign guy.
白宫顾问，克林顿的助选员
The one with the great hair, sexy smile,cute butt.
他有迷人的头发性感的微笑 带劲儿的屁股?
Oh,him! The little guy. Oh,I love him!
是他!那个小矮人? 我好喜欢他
-Wait. Wait,I see a woman. -T ell me it's his mother.
-等等，我看一个女人 -告诉我那是他妈
-Definitely not his mother. -Oh,no!
-绝对不是他妈 -不
Wait,she's walking across the floor. She's walking,she's walking....
慢着，她走过地板 她走着…她走着…她走着…
She's going for the pizza That's not for you,bitch!
她去拿披萨了 不是给你的，臭女人
We've been here for over an hour, and people less sick have gone in.
抱歉，我们已等了一个小时 许多情况比我朋友轻的人都走了
That guy with the toe thing, who's he sleeping with?
那个脚趾上挂东西的 他和谁睡觉?
Oh,come on,Dora. Don't be mad.
朵拉，别生气
I know we both said some things...
我知道我们都说了些…伤害彼此的话
...we didn't mean but that doesn't mean we still don't love each other.
但那不意味着我们不再爱着对方
You know,I feel like I've lost her.
我想她不会再理我了
-Come on,push me. -No.
-来吧，推我 -不
-Push me. -We' re gonna get in trouble.
-来吧，推我 -我们碰到麻烦了
Don't be a baby. Push me. Push me.
不要像个小孩子一样.推我,推我
All right. I' m gonna push you,okay? How about I push you like this?
好吧,我要推了你哦,准备好了吗? 不如我像这样推你吧
Now you're gonna be in a wheelchair the rest of your life,pally-wally....
现在你将在轮椅上度过你的余生, 我亲密的朋友
I am so very sorry. Can I sign you?
非常对不起,我能给你签名吗？
-Lights still out? -Yeah.
-灯还关着,对吗? -是的
Well,maybe they' re napping.
或许他们在小睡
-Please. They' re having sex. -Shut up!
-拜托，他们在做爱 -闭嘴
So,what do you think George is like?
你们认为史先生是什么样的人?
-I think he's shy. -Yeah.
-我认为他很害羞 -真的?
Yeah. I think you have to draw him out.
你必须勾引他
And then when you do, he's a preppy animal.
之后他就会渐渐显露出兽性
-What do you think of the guys? -Our guys?
-你们认为这些小伙怎么样? -我们的小伙们?
-Yeah,our guys. -I feel funny talking about that.
-是的，我们的小伙 -提到他们我就觉得很有趣
-Oh,come on. -Okay. Well....
-来嘛 -好吧…
I think Joey's like a little kiddie ride.
我觉得乔伊就像…一个小骑手
You just have to put the quarter in and it just goes.
你只用把他放在角落里，它自然会走
He might surprise you. One time, he helped me put on my coat...
他也许会给你惊喜. 有一次，他帮我穿上外套…
...and he was really tender.
…他真的很体贴
Come on,baby,come on. Let's go.
来吧，我们走
Yes!
好的！
Chandler's one of those repressed guys who you'd have to seduce.
钱德是一个感情内敛的小伙 你必须劝他才能上床
I think it's an act. Chandler is more sophisticated than he seems.
我觉得就像是一处戏 钱德比他实际看起来能有内涵
-You know who's kind of sexy? -Don't.
-你知道谁有那种性感嘛? -我不清楚
-Ross. -No,guys. Please,he is my brother.
-罗斯 -不会吧，他是我哥哥
I know exactly what you mean. He can be really smooth.
我完全明白你的意思 他真的很沉稳
Can't you just picture him in bed?
你能想象他在床上的样子吗?
I really don't want to.
我一点也不想
Come on,laugh. Laugh.
来吧，笑一个
I remember the moonlight coming in the window,and her face had the most...
我记得月光透过窗户照进来 她的脸庞露出…
...incredible glow.
…无比甜蜜的微笑
The moon,the glow, the magical feeling. You did this.
月光，微笑 魔幻的感觉，说得好
Could I get some painkillers over here,please?
谁能拿点止痛药来吗?
He's right. Enough. What's the big deal about today?
他说得对，你够了没? 今天有什么大不了的?
So you slept with her for the first time.
你和她第一次上床，了不起?
You slept with her for seven years after that.
之后你又和她做了七年
It's a little more complicated
事情没那么简单
What is it,that she left you for another woman that likes women?
那么问题出在哪儿?她把你甩了? 她爱上女人?
Louder. There's a man on the 1 2th floor in a coma who didn't hear you.
大声点，行吗? 12楼有个昏迷的人听不清楚
Then,what?
然后呢?
My first time with Carol was...
我和卡萝的第一次
...was my....
…是我的…
What?
什么?
It was my first time.
是我的第一次
With Carol?
和卡萝?
Oh.
噢
So,in your whole life, you've only been with one?
这么说你这辈子只和一人…
Oh,boy. Hockey was a big mistake.
天啊，看曲棍球真是个错误
There's a bunch of stuff we could've done tonight.
本来今晚我们可以干很多事
Okay,I got one.
我有了
Do you remember that vegetarian pate...
你记得我做的那个蔬菜面团吗…?
...that I made that you loved so much?
…你非常喜欢的那个
Well,unless goose is a vegetable!
好吧，除非鹅也是蔬菜
Now I don't feel so bad about sleeping with Jason Hurley.
和强森上床的感觉没那么糟
-What? You slept with Jason? -You had already broken up.
-什么?你和强森上床? -你们已经分手了
-How long? -Just a couple hours.
-多久之后? -几小时
-Oh,that's nice! -Okay,okay,okay,I got one!
-真好 -我也有了
Anyway,the valentine T om left in your locker was really from me!
情人节汤姆放在你置物箱的东西 其实是我放的
Excuse me?
什么?
Hello! Like he was really gonna send you one.
你以为他真会送你东西?
She was a big girl!
她太天真了
Really? Well,at least big girls don't pee in their pants in seventh grade!
真的?天真的女孩 至少不会在七年级时还尿裤子
I was laughing. You made me laugh!
当时我是在笑，你逗得我大笑
Oh,my God! There he is! There he is!
他来了,他来了
-Where? -Where we've been looking all night.
-在哪儿? -我们看了一整夜的地方
-He's so cute. -George,baby,drop the towel.
-他真帅 -我的宝贝乔治，快拿掉浴巾
-Come on,drop the towel. -Drop it. Will you please drop it?
- 快拿掉浴巾…  - 一次就好
Wow!
哇!
Man,can you believe he's only had sex with one woman?
你能相信他只和一个女人上过床?
I think it's great. You know,it's sweet.
这样很好啊 甜蜜
It's romantic.
又浪漫
Really?
你真的这样认为?
You kidding? The guy's a freak. I judge him.
才怪,这家伙是怪胎，我要审判他
-Hey,man! -Hey,buddy!
-老兄 -兄弟
Oh,that's attractive.
真是迷人
I thought you were great in Silence of the Lambs.
你在《沉默的羔羊》里演得真好
Admit it,all things considered, you had fun tonight.
快承认吧,纵观一切，你今晚很开心
Fun? Where was the fun? T ell me which part was fun.
开心?哪里开心? 告诉哪一点值得我开心?
Where's my puck?
我的曲棍球在哪儿?
-The kid has it. -The kid
-在那小孩手里 -孩子…
Excuse me,that's my puck.
球是我的
I found it. Finders keepers,losers weepers.
我找到的 谁发现归谁，丢掉的人活该
You gotta do it,man.
争气点
I' m rubber,you' re glue. Whatever you
是吗?我是橡胶你是胶水…
I can't do it.
我做不到
-Listen,give me back my puck. -No.
-还我，到底还不还我 -我不
-Yes,how about? -No.
-过来，不如这样? -不行
-Give me my puck. -No.
-球还我 -不
No roughhousing in my ER!
别在我这儿闹事
Give me my puck!
把球还我
Now that was fun.
那才叫好玩
Okay,Monica. Right foot,red.
摩妮卡，右脚红
We could've played Monopoly,but no!
本来我们是要玩大富翁的?
Thanks.
谢了
Okay,Pheebs. Right hand,blue.
菲此，右手蓝
Ross,switch with me and Phoebe could be number two.
罗斯,和我换一下 菲比应该是2号
Nothing. It's a Twister thing. The rules are on the back of the box.
不行,这是钮钮乐. 规则就在盒子的背后
Hello?
你好?
It's the Visa card people.
信用卡人员打来的
-Okay. Will you take my place? -All right. This is Rachel.
-好，愿意代替我吗? -我是瑞秋
No!
不!
Hello? Oh,yeah. No,I know. I haven't been using it much.
不，我知道，我很久没用了
Oh,well,thanks. But l' m okay,really.
谢了，我没事，真的
-To the green. -Oh,no.
-绿色的,到绿色那里.  -噢，不
I've got magic beans.
我有魔豆
No,no,never mind.
不，当我没说
T o the left! T o the left!
左转，左转
I' m fine.
我没事